

https://github.com/taistr

# Personal Summary

Adaptable, organised, sociable, and quick-thinking; I have experience working to deadlines, in environments that require a keen technical proficiency, efficiency and accuracy. I am curious and driven and cannot spend too long with my head outside of a project either for my student team or myself. Outside of my studies and work I enjoy dabbling electronics, robotics, and software development.

## Experience

June 2021 - Present

Electrical Hardware Engineer, Monash Human Power

I currently do some work on the electrical sub-team at Monash Human Power.

- I completed a project in August 2021 involving designing and manufacturing a replacement HDMI converter printed circuit board using KiCad.
- I am currently working on adding a new strain gauge sensor to the bike for additional telemetry during riding and for verification of CFD simulations.

Jan. 2021 - Present

Front Desk Attendant / PC Technician, Computerbank Victoria Inc

I volunteer at Computerbank Victoria (typically on Saturdays). On any given week we may require that donations be processed, new computers be built, support requests be booked or customers to be served in the showroom and throughout the day I will be filling in one or more of these roles.

Aug. 2019 - Present

Academic Tutor, Learnmate Tutoring Pty

Outside of project-work and volunteering I have been doing private tutoring for 2 years. I teach secondary school mathematics and physics up to the VCE 3-4 level. As of 2021, I do work for both parents/students who have contacted me through Learnmate or directly. I taught in-person prior to the 2021 lockdown but have since swapped to fully online via zoom or Learnmate's online platform. I have also recently joined Alchemy Tuition.

### **Skills**

- Programming proficient in C, MATLAB, Python, Verilog, Javascript, HTML and CSS (w/ SCSS) and always willing to pick up a few more!
- Tools and Environments: Familiar with Linux (Manjaro, Raspbian and Mint), Windows and MacOS. I use Git for version control and Figma for preliminary designs.
- Computer hardware experience working on and using microcontroller boards (Arduino boards), sensors and a variety of computer hardware ranging from single board computers (Raspberry Pi family) up to desktop systems.
- PCB design experience designing printed circuit boards in CAD software (KiCad) and SMD soldering.
- Proficient with Github, KiCad, Adobe Creative Suite, Office Suite, Libre Suite, Da Vinci Resolve 17.
- Web Development basic experience with front-end web development.
  - o A few of my web development projects can be found on my github profile (see top right).
- Tutoring a reflective tutor with a keen interest in making even the most complex concepts intuitive.

#### Education

2021 - Present Bachelor of Engineering (Honours), Monash University

- Masters Accelerated Pathway
- Robotics and Mechatronics Engineering Artificial Intelligence

2018 - 2020 Victorian Certificate of Education (VCE), Suzanne Cory High School

- English Language, Mathematical Methods, Specialist Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry, Software Development
- Academic Excellence Award (2019)
- Silver Community Engagement Award (2019)
- Silver Community Engagement Award (2020)

### Certifications

- 2021 Working with Children Check
- 2020 Responsible Service of Alcohol (RSA) Certificate, VCGLR
- **2019** 5<sup>th</sup> Class Taekwondo Referee Certificate, Australian Taekwondo